

Ahmed Sayed

Senior Graphic Designer

ABOUT ME

Hi, my name is ahmed, I'm a graphic designer with great attention to detail and possess over 7 years of experience in the graphic design industry. I specialize in Print and social design and an expertise in the following design tools: Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and final cut pro x.

LENGUAGES

ARABIC

ENGLISH

HOBBIES







MUSIC

ART

I FADN

CONTACT INFO



01023297562



aahhmmeeddsayed@gmail.com



GIZA, EGYPT



Ahmed Sayed



WORK EXPERIENCE

free art

2021-2022

Graphic designer

I design all kinds of prints, especially posters and cards and bellpord

EGYPT KIDS

2019 - 2020

Graphic designer

I do social media designs and design prints for everything special for children

freelanceing

2015 - 2022

Graphic desiger & Vedio editing

do anything



EDUCATION

Higher Institute for Specific Studies in Giza 2019 - 2022

Good

Information and systems specialization



SKILLS

Graphic design

Print design

Banner design

Social media posting

Video editing

Flyer design

Instagram post design

Photo editing



SOFTWARE

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR

FINAL CUT PRO X

MICROSOFT OFFICE

BEHANCE LINK

https://www.behance.net/ahmmedsaayeed

